好吧，这1232年，所以让我们分开吧，我确定雨是
all right this 1232 so let's part I am sure the rain is a
so let's part I am sure the rain is a factor on some not coming on time so
某些时间不准的因素，所以在这些讲座之后，我认为
factor on some not coming on time so behind these lectures I thought that
behind these lectures I thought that hidden Markov models will work them in
隐藏的马尔可夫模型将在过去使用它们，但至少基于问题
hidden Markov models will work them in the past but based on at least questions
the past but based on at least questions I have from two of you I don't know why
我有两个人，我不知道为什么要捡起很多东西
I have from two of you I don't know why some kind of having picked up lots of
some kind of having picked up lots of the ideas because we already cover the
这些想法，因为我们已经用hmm弥补了算法的损失，但是
the ideas because we already cover the loss of the algorithms with hmm but
loss of the algorithms with hmm but maybe you only pick up ideas after the
也许你只有在做完作业后才想到主意，我想你会认识你吗？
maybe you only pick up ideas after the homework shall I assume you know you
homework shall I assume you know you have to work on the homework and then
必须要做功课，然后事情就很清楚了，所以无论如何，我必须
have to work on the homework and then things are clear so anyways so I have to
things are clear so anyways so I have to spend maybe 10 mins to repeat some of
可能要花10分钟来重复我们之前讨论过的一些事情
spend maybe 10 mins to repeat some of the things we discussed on the previous
the things we discussed on the previous lecture even though they were not very
演讲虽然不是很重要，但我不是很困难
lecture even though they were not very essential I mean not very difficulties
essential I mean not very difficulties so let me go back to 166 hopefully you
所以让我回到166，希望你们都得到了幻灯片，所以维琪做了
so let me go back to 166 hopefully you all got the slide so Vicki made
all got the slide so Vicki made everybody so when we discuss on
每个人，所以当我们讨论估计隐藏的参数时
everybody so when we discuss on estimating the parameters of a hidden
estimating the parameters of a hidden Markov model from observations on the
根据对变量X的观察得出的马尔可夫模型，我们必须如此有效地
Markov model from observations on the variables X so effectively we have to
variables X so effectively we have to compete with other parameter star on
在Z的初始分布P上与其他参数星竞争
compete with other parameter star on this initial distribution P of Z one of
this initial distribution P of Z one of these transition matrix in this
在给定的ZT减去1的情况下，此概率城市中的这些转换矩阵
these transition matrix in this probability city given ZT minus 1 and
probability city given ZT minus 1 and whatever unknowns we have on the
不管我们在观察中有什么未知数，哦，对不起
whatever unknowns we have on the observation what oh I'm sorry on the
observation what oh I'm sorry on the yeah on the on the you know on the
是的，在您知道测量分布上的东西
yeah on the on the you know on the measurement distribution the the things
measurement distribution the the things that I basically covered on the last
我在上一讲中基本上讲到的实际上与什么无关
that I basically covered on the last lecture are really independent of what
lecture are really independent of what type of distribution we assume for the
给定隐藏状态，我们假设XT的概率分布类型
type of distribution we assume for the probability of XT given the hidden state
probability of XT given the hidden state so you can have a Gaussian and a multi
所以你可以有一个高斯分布和一个多新分布
so you can have a Gaussian and a multi newly distribution you can they have
newly distribution you can they have whatever this sort of is generic and
不管这种类型是通用的，然后您都必须做一些特别的事情
whatever this sort of is generic and then you have to do something special
then you have to do something special about
关于提高上学期的参数
about raising the parameters of the last term
raising the parameters of the last term okay simple statement serious you cannot
好吧，简单的声明，严重的是，您不能真正将Z集成出来，因为
okay simple statement serious you cannot really go and integrate Z out because
really go and integrate Z out because that will require a massive calculation
这将需要大量的计算，因此您需要做的是
that will require a massive calculation so what you need to do is you need to be
so what you need to do is you need to be able to estimate the parameters with the
能够以估计的最大似然排序来估计参数
able to estimate the parameters with the maximum likelihood sort of an estimate
maximum likelihood sort of an estimate you need to work with their expectation
您需要使用他们的期望最大化算法，我知道我
you need to work with their expectation maximization algorithm and I you know I
maximization algorithm and I you know I provided the specifics for the case of
提供了嗯的情况的细节，但实际上是拳头在同一家
provided the specifics for the case of hmm but really fist the same home where
hmm but really fist the same home where in in many other areas of machine
在机器学习的许多其他领域中，所以接下来与阿尔伯特重复
in in many other areas of machine learning so next repeat with the Albert
learning so next repeat with the Albert looks like extra mass transfer next one
看起来像是多余的传质接下来，我们对X Capital TZ说：
looks like extra mass transfer next one let's say to X capital T Z are they
let's say to X capital T Z are they affiliated latent variables we don't
关联的潜在变量，我们不知道他们是谁
affiliated latent variables we don't know what they are people of the
know what they are people of the parameters all right so whether it is
参数好，所以是否弱，这是联合的可能性
parameters all right so whether it is weak form this is the joint likelihood
weak form this is the joint likelihood usually the recipient of observations
通常是观察对象的接收者，所以很明显Z未被观察到，但是
usually the recipient of observations right so obviously Z is not observed but
right so obviously Z is not observed but this is the this distribution is written
这是该分布是作为函数编写的，并且发布了信息
this is the this distribution is written as a function and the posted information
as a function and the posted information variable Z it's also function of
变量Z也是参数的函数，所以我们要做的是创建一个
variable Z it's also function of parameter so what we do is to create an
在以前的值上更新此值，这是对生命联合的期望
update this on the previous values this is the expectation of the joint of life
is the expectation of the joint of life it will be respect to this posterior and
这将是关于这个后验的，期望步骤基本上是
it will be respect to this posterior and the expectation step is basically to
the expectation step is basically to compute this whole term Q all right do
计算整个项Q可以进行计算，然后
compute this whole term Q all right do the calculations and then the
the calculations and then the maximization is once we compute it
最大化是我们计算出的相对于theta和
maximization is once we compute it optimize it with respect to theta and
optimize it with respect to theta and once we do that then you come back to
一旦我们做到了，那么您将回到第一步以完成此操作
once we do that then you come back to the first step to complete this with
the first step to complete this with theta being taking now that all the
现在theta正在获取所有第五次幂，并再次更新theta
theta being taking now that all the fifth power all and again updating theta
fifth power all and again updating theta etcetera etcetera okay hmm in other
etcetera etcetera好吧，嗯，在其他地方，你会得到足够的不同
etcetera etcetera okay hmm in other place you will get different sufficient
place you will get different sufficient statistics the sufficient statistics
统计他们即将到来的足够的统计数据
statistics the sufficient statistics that they were coming up where
that they were coming up where effectively this is moving distribution
有效地，这是移动分布伽马，这是GT的伽马
effectively this is moving distribution gamma this is gamma of G T which is the
gamma this is gamma of G T which is the probability of Z little T given all the
给定所有数据后Z的概率为T
probability of Z little T given all the data and again compute at the old
data and again compute at the old parameters so this is a smoking
参数，所以这是一个吸烟分布，因为我们正在估算Z
parameters so this is a smoking distribution because we are estimating Z
distribution because we are estimating Z at some time T given day the way past
在给定日期T的某个时间，通过此数据，我们从时间0到3
at some time T given day the way past three by this our data from time 0 to
three by this our data from time 0 to time capital T and then we also needed
时间资本T，然后我们还需要Z t的联合吸烟分布
time capital T and then we also needed the joint smoking distribution of Z t
the joint smoking distribution of Z t minus 1 DT okay and I'm going to remind
负1 DT好吧，我今天要提醒您，我们已经看到了
minus 1 DT okay and I'm going to remind you today and we have seen these
you today and we have seen these calculations from 12 is are coming so
来自12的计算即将到来，所以这是CT的联合分布
calculations from 12 is are coming so this is the Joint Distribution of CT
this is the Joint Distribution of CT minus 1 and city now ZT is let's say we
负1和现在的城市ZT可以说我们有K个州，所以这是一个
minus 1 and city now ZT is let's say we have K States all right so this is a
have K States all right so this is a vector at this time of vector of
此时的向量为维K的向量，并且该对称状态为
vector at this time of vector of dimension K and this symmetric state by
dimension K and this symmetric state by K okay in this recipe in this problem
这次在这个问题的食谱中可以找到足够的统计数据
K okay in this recipe in this problem this time the sufficient statistics that
this time the sufficient statistics that you need to compute the joint of
从本质上讲，您需要计算似然联合
you need to compute the joint of likelihood in essence all the
likelihood in essence all the information you need to extract from the
您需要从数据中提取的信息是列表，现在可以了，您
information you need to extract from the data is list and that ok now this you
data is list and that ok now this you know I already have you know discussed
知道我已经有您知道的讨论了，然后我们才开始
know I already have you know discussed this before we're going to basically
this before we're going to basically need to do that for words mark wants
需要这样做，因为单词标记想弄乱就禁食了，因为基本上
need to do that for words mark wants messed is fasting okay because basically
messed is fasting okay because basically this gamma is the product of alpha and
此gamma是alpha和beta消息的产物，但是您知道您可以
this gamma is the product of alpha and beta messages but you know you can do a
beta messages but you know you can do a llama decryption and we already have
骆驼解密，我们已经看到了
llama decryption and we already have seen that as well and
seen that as well and first I'll show you know will become if
首先，我会告诉你，如果你做的很好，它将成为后向传递
first I'll show you know will become if you do it for good the backward passing
you do it for good the backward passing you can calculate this on the fly as
您也可以随时计算这个，所以我们不需要这个
you can calculate this on the fly as well alright so we don't need this let
well alright so we don't need this let me just go to review very fast I two
我两天前去复习的速度非常快，所以当我总结时，我们必须
me just go to review very fast I two days ago so when I sum we have to
days ago so when I sum we have to calculate one of Z T right zippy can
计算一个正确的ZT zippy可以取K值，所以我们实际上取它们
calculate one of Z T right zippy can take K values so we actually take them
take K values so we actually take them escape analysis to calculate one of ZT k
逸出分析以计算ZT k之一，所以你能告诉我这是神秘的吗
escape analysis to calculate one of ZT k so can you tell me this is mystically so
so can you tell me this is mystically so when I shall teach and a time indicator
当我教书时，时间指示器的保养是一个直接的指示器，那么什么是
when I shall teach and a time indicator care is a straight indicator so what is
care is a straight indicator so what is very much city K so we know that we're
非常多的城市K，所以我们知道我们在谈论同样的事情
very much city K so we know that we're talking about the same things the
talking about the same things the probability is that
可能性是
所以凯撒的系统概率权是一个挑剔的移动分布
talking about the same things the probability is that
so the system probability right Caesar is a fastidious moving distribution
所以凯撒的系统概率权是一个挑剔的移动分布
is a fastidious moving distribution doesn't credit accounts so it what is
没有记入帐户，所以它是与衰变相对的伽玛，我提醒您
doesn't credit accounts so it what is gamma opposite decay and I remind you
gamma opposite decay and I remind you again I kept no one to keep going back
再次，我没有人再回去花十分钟去做，所以这是
again I kept no one to keep going back to takes ten minutes to do so this is
to takes ten minutes to do so this is the definition of the veteran CT gamma Z
老兵CT伽玛Z T的定义
the definition of the veteran CT gamma Z T it's the post a diversity given all
T it's the post a diversity given all the data from time one to time capital T
从一次到一次的资本T的数据，所以当我把
the data from time one to time capital T so what this gram of ZT k when I put the
so what this gram of ZT k when I put the index there explicitly so this is a
在那里明确地索引，所以这是一个数字，不是向量，所以是什么
index there explicitly so this is a number is not a vector right so what is
number is not a vector right so what is gamma of Z DK is the probability of
Z DK的伽玛是
因此，我们基本上将其发送给该机构，他们向他们派遣了西班牙的任务，而这
number is not a vector right so what is gamma of Z DK is the probability of
we sent it so basically this agency decay Spanish missions to them and this
因此，我们基本上将其发送给该机构，他们向他们派遣了西班牙的任务，而这
decay Spanish missions to them and this is the posterior probability that they
是他们接受值的后验概率，如果
is the posterior probability that they will take the value up okay and if the
will take the value up okay and if the values are 1 and 0 obviously this is the
值分别为1和0，这与ztk的期望值相同
values are 1 and 0 obviously this is the same is the expectation of ztk right
same is the expectation of ztk right because the expectation is the value at
因为期望值是x1乘以概率乘以另一个的值
because the expectation is the value at x1 times the probability times the other
x1 times the probability times the other value 0 times the probability so it's
值是概率的0倍，所以它实际上等于
value 0 times the probability so it's really equal to the probability that
really equal to the probability that typically is equal to 1 what's the
通常等于1的后验概率是多少，当然您
typically is equal to 1 what's the posterior probability and certainly you
posterior probability and certainly you can think this as this joint expectation
可以以一种非常相似的方式认为这是这种共同的期望
can think this as this joint expectation in a very similar fashion from time that
in a very similar fashion from time that they wanted capital T all right so this
他们想要大写的T，所以这是我的大写X，我们要
they wanted capital T all right so this is my capital X and we're going to
is my capital X and we're going to calculate this Q and when you remember
计算这个Q，当你记得丹尼是对联合的期望时
calculate this Q and when you remember Danny is the expectation of the joint of
Danny is the expectation of the joint of likelihood this is y so actually just
可能是y，所以实际上再次提醒我，这个伽玛是怎么来的
likelihood this is y so actually just remind me again how did this gamma come
remind me again how did this gamma come here at how the tea came the other let's
这里是茶是怎么来的，另一个让我们看看这个理论是什么时候第二次
here at how the tea came the other let's look at this theory when did this second
look at this theory when did this second from this term there
从这个学期开始
和泉办公室在温度中可能讨论了在可能的回报中撰写
look at this theory when did this second from this term there
kazumi office in temperature probably discussed writing in the likely return
和泉办公室在温度中可能讨论了在可能的回报中撰写
discussed writing in the likely return this was let's say this was the
可以说这是从J过渡到K的概率
this was let's say this was the probability of transitioning from J to K
probability of transitioning from J to K which is from J to K so this would be a
这是从J到K的，所以这将是一个JK-这是什么^指标函数
which is from J to K so this would be a JK - what ^ indicator function that this
JK - what ^ indicator function that this term here is the K term of that is equal
此处的K项等于1，对不起，
term here is the K term of that is equal to 1 and that the I'm sorry that the
to 1 and that the I'm sorry that the j-turn or that's equal to 1 and that the
右转或等于1，而后约等于1右，然后
j-turn or that's equal to 1 and that the later about is equal to 1 right and the
later about is equal to 1 right and the function when you take the expectations
当您对后验有期望时起作用
function when you take the expectations with respect to the posterior what do
with respect to the posterior what do you get you get that all right
你得到你一切都好，与此类似，你得到这个，
you get you get that all right and similarly from this you get this and
and similarly from this you get this and here I'm assuming that the observation
在这里，我假设观察模型有一个用于
here I'm assuming that the observation model there is one observation model for
model there is one observation model for each state K so for the state K
每个状态K因此对于状态K基本上观察到它将是P
each state K so for the state K basically observation what it would be P
basically observation what it would be P of XT given 3 K 4 PK of the parameters
XT的给定，该期望模型中涉及的参数为3 K 4 PK，因此
of XT given 3 K 4 PK of the parameters involved in this expectation model so to
involved in this expectation model so to be able to do the expectation step on
能够对您要计算的EM算法执行期望步骤
be able to do the expectation step on the EM algorithm you have to compute
the EM algorithm you have to compute this gamma you have to compute XT and
这个伽玛，你必须计算XT，当然你知道这两个术语
this gamma you have to compute XT and and of course you know these two terms
and of course you know these two terms here required and in this term requires
这是必需的，在这个学期中，需要4个，但在
here required and in this term requires 4 with but with message passing at the
4 with but with message passing at the same thing with itself there is step is
本身也有相同的步骤，基本上是采取这些方法的导数
same thing with itself there is step is to basically take derivatives of these
to basically take derivatives of these things with respect to PK and their
关于PK的事物和关于H的单位说K，所以它是
things with respect to PK and their units with respect to H say K so it's
units with respect to H say K so it's simple calculus okay the only thing is
简单的演算好了，唯一的事情是当您考虑到该单位的
simple calculus okay the only thing is when you take the unit's with respect to
when you take the unit's with respect to B K you have to put in advance
BK您必须提前乘数，因为P的时间
B K you have to put in advance multiplier because the time for the P
multiplier because the time for the P K's
大写的K个州中的K等于1
K's over the capital K States is equal to 1
over the capital K States is equal to 1 very very differentiated take the units
非常非常微分，取等于0的单位，基本上
very very differentiated take the units equal to 0 you get basically
equal to 0 you get basically PK to be equal dot and a JK equal to 1
PK等于点，JK等于1可以，那么英国的行动是
PK to be equal dot and a JK equal to 1 okay and then the British action is
okay and then the British action is exactly what you will expect as an
正是您期望得到的正确答案范围K
exactly what you will expect as an answer right range a K the
answer right range a K the the Emily estimate is the number of
艾米丽（Emily）估算值是您从状态说转变的次数
the Emily estimate is the number of times that you transition from state say
times that you transition from state say to carry over have different time
进行具有不同时间瞬间的ISTE，然后将其除以
to carry over have different time instants ISTE right and divide it by the
instants ISTE right and divide it by the time square developed state J and the
时代广场发展到状态J并过渡到由
time square developed state J and the transition to anything given by the
transition to anything given by the label level L equal 1 to capital K make
标签级别L等于1等于大写K
label level L equal 1 to capital K make some sense okay
如果您给出的答案当然取决于观察模型，则无需计算
no calculation for the observation model if the answers you gave of course depend
if the answers you gave of course depend on what observation model you have so
您有什么样的观察模型，让我们说观察员是否自愿
on what observation model you have so let's say if the observation volunteers
let's say if the observation volunteers that contain small as a Gaussian and the
包含小如高斯和每个状态k的未知数对我来说
that contain small as a Gaussian and the unknowns for each state k is me to the
unknowns for each state k is me to the mean and the covariance basically then
均值和协方差基本上取了我上一次的导数
mean and the covariance basically then taking derivatives of the last time I
taking derivatives of the last time I mean Q basically leaving this is the
均值Q基本上离开这是该系数出现的唯一位置
mean Q basically leaving this is the only place where this coefficients come
only place where this coefficients come so really you won't get any effect from
所以实际上您不会从那里得到任何效果，所以如果您将
so really you won't get any effect from there so if you take the log of the
there so if you take the log of the Gaussian and you differentiate you
高斯和你区分你有效地得到了四十岁，你得到了
Gaussian and you differentiate you effectively get forties did you get the
effectively get forties did you get the UK is the weighted average of all the
英国是所有观测值X 3的加权平均值，但此比率为
UK is the weighted average of all the observations X 3 but this rate is with
observations X 3 but this rate is with respect to this procedure
尊重此程序的责任逗号实际上是
respect to this procedure responsibilities comma right actually
responsibilities comma right actually that is the reason we call gamma to be
这就是我们称伽玛为后继责任的原因，
that is the reason we call gamma to be the posterior responsibilities and
the posterior responsibilities and similarly you get 4 Sigma K the same
同样，您得到4 Sigma K，就像采样协方差一样
similarly you get 4 Sigma K the same thing this is like the sample covariance
thing this is like the sample covariance but now it's you notice is weighted by
但是现在您注意到，这是由后验可能性来加权的
but now it's you notice is weighted by the posterior possibilities this is
the posterior possibilities this is identical effectively with estimating
与估计高斯混合中的系数完全相同
identical effectively with estimating the coefficients in a Gaussian mixture
the coefficients in a Gaussian mixture all right because as we know the you
好的，因为我们知道您知道hmm模型，但这在
all right because as we know the you know the hmm model but this in the
know the hmm model but this in the context of wearing the parameters is not
佩戴参数的上下文与估计的相差不大
context of wearing the parameters is not very much different from the estimated
very much different from the estimated parameters in the Gaussian mixture maybe
高斯混合中的参数也许应该是想给你一些
parameters in the Gaussian mixture maybe should be wants to give you some
should be wants to give you some homework some calculating those things
功课一些计算这些事情好吧，他们每个人都像5行，但
homework some calculating those things ok they each of them is like 5 lines but
ok they each of them is like 5 lines but in Ephesus to will force you to do the
在以弗所会强迫你做代数并找出例如
in Ephesus to will force you to do the algebra and figure out for example here
algebra and figure out for example here that Bernoulli observation model or a
伯努利观测模型或您知道的多单元装置可以做到这一点
that Bernoulli observation model or a multi unit you know to do this
multi unit you know to do this calculations correct and not sure to
计算正确，并且不确定要理解这是什么意思
calculations correct and not sure to understand what this meaning side
understand what this meaning side because if you have a little bit small
因为如果您有一点小提防的话，也许是很小的账单就可以了
because if you have a little bit small beware maybe a very small bill all right
beware maybe a very small bill all right so you know you ever have to give us a
所以您知道您曾经必须给我们提供多个年金分配，所以这
so you know you ever have to give us a multi annuity distribution so this
multi annuity distribution so this calculation stuff basically
计算的东西基本上很简单，只有几行
calculation stuff basically straightforward with just a few lines of
straightforward with just a few lines of calculations okay
计算好吧，我记得我已经离开了，但让我
calculations okay I remember I'm left with this but let me
I remember I'm left with this but let me just say the the following which
只需说出以下内容，当您尝试学习以下内容时
just say the the following which sometimes when you try to to learn the
sometimes when you try to to learn the parameters with one dataset from the
需要花费时间资本T的花费时间从一个数据集中获得的参数
parameters with one dataset from the take time you want the time capital T so
take time you want the time capital T so you live data basically on one pass over
您实际上是通过火车一次传递数据的，也许该数据不是
you live data basically on one pass over the train maybe the data is not an
the train maybe the data is not an obstacle to making the parameters
设置参数的障碍，因为如果您认为自己有一个
obstacle to making the parameters because if you think that you have an
because if you think that you have an XML mangled up is from a satellite so
XML是来自卫星的，因此您可以向后退，所以一旦我们移动
XML mangled up is from a satellite so you can go backwards so once we move
you can go backwards so once we move speak to you never go back to say - so
跟你说话永远不要回话-这样你就没有足够的信息说
speak to you never go back to say - so you won't have enough information to say
you won't have enough information to say to cut made the transition from due to
削减从过渡到由于你只有一个方程
to cut made the transition from due to slightly you only have one equation
slightly you only have one equation information to help you to do that so in
可以帮助您做到这一点的信息，在这种情况下，重复进行是有帮助的
information to help you to do that so in that case what it helps is to repeat
that case what it helps is to repeat this not for one data set all right each
这不是针对一个数据集，好吧，每个数据集都是来自
this not for one data set all right each of them being a sequence of data from
of them being a sequence of data from time wanna take the time Ti so basically
要花时间Ti，所以基本上我们会在这张幻灯片中做的，我是
time wanna take the time Ti so basically we would have done in this slide and I'm
we would have done in this slide and I'm not going to go through all of the
不会经历所有的计算是完全相同的
not going to go through all of the calculations are exactly the same
calculations are exactly the same results that I had before the only thing
我之前唯一改变过的结果
results that I had before the only thing that I have changed this in the
that I have changed this in the sufficient statistics by the summation
通过汇总得出足够的统计信息
当然，如果您喜欢每个火车，我们都会知道火车的持续时间。
that I have changed this in the sufficient statistics by the summation
of course you know the duration of the train if you like that each of them we
当然，如果您喜欢每个火车，我们都会知道火车的持续时间。
train if you like that each of them we have a different duration from let's say
与时间1 2 TI具有相同的持续时间，但是可以
have a different duration from let's say time 1 2 TI right to be the same but can
time 1 2 TI right to be the same but can be different but so the only thing I
会有所不同，但我唯一拥有的与以前有所不同
be different but so the only thing I have is different from before varies
have is different from before varies estimation capital n capital n is how
估计资本n资本n是您知道多少个结
estimation capital n capital n is how many knots you know how many capital
many knots you know how many capital extra stuff I had before I have provided
在我提供给您之前，我有多余的东西，因为大写的X是时间的数据
extra stuff I had before I have provided you because capital X was data from time
you because capital X was data from time wanted to T now I give you n approach
想现在就开始，我给你个办法，好吧，关于那件事，
wanted to T now I give you n approach okay so about the only thing that
okay so about the only thing that changes the rest remains basically
改变其余部分基本上仍然保留在磁带中，如果
changes the rest remains basically in veins the tape let me go fastest if
in veins the tape let me go fastest if there is anything interesting
有什么有趣的事
然后，如果您没有看到它，我们将摆脱这种情况
in veins the tape let me go fastest if there is anything interesting
and then we would get out of this in case you have not seen it for example
然后，如果您没有看到它，我们将摆脱这种情况
case you have not seen it for example when I knew this is the yep alright what
当我知道这是对，您可以做的是，您可以增强自己的能力
when I knew this is the yep alright what you can do is you can enhance your
you can do is you can enhance your business best friend anomaly estimate
业务最好的朋友异常估计正确，因此您可以在
business best friend anomaly estimate right so you can put something in the
right so you can put something in the parameters and immediately transform of
参数，然后立即将其转换为办公室，这是微不足道的
parameters and immediately transform of this to an office and that's the trivial
this to an office and that's the trivial calculation so if you look at maybe
计算，因此，如果您看的是书本，甚至有人给您打电话
calculation so if you look at maybe books or even people give this as a call
books or even people give this as a call mark maybe
马克也许苏比克想给你这个作为
mark maybe Subic wants to give you this as a
Subic wants to give you this as a homework you can put some prior on 5k
您可以在5k上先放一些作业，然后在JK上放火
homework you can put some prior on 5k some fire on a JK and base you can
some fire on a JK and base you can before if you remember what we did is we
如果您还记得我们所做的，那我们就让我发疯了可能性模型
before if you remember what we did is we started me crazy the likelihood model
started me crazy the likelihood model like that so now that you will base you
这样，您现在就可以拥有现代的可能性了
like that so now that you will base you have the likelihood modern times the
have the likelihood modern times the probability law the parameters and then
概率定律参数，然后将完全相同的计算
probability law the parameters and then be exactly the same calculation you will
be exactly the same calculation you will just give contribution from the much of
只是从很多先验中做出贡献，但是最终当你这样做时
just give contribution from the much of the priors but eventually when you do
the priors but eventually when you do that I am aware that you will give you
我知道您会给我我对参数的估计，并且
that I am aware that you will give you my estimates for the parameters and that
my estimates for the parameters and that standard okay
标准可以让您知道良好的结果，特别是
standard okay to get you know good results especially
to get you know good results especially when we have limited data okay
当我们的数据有限时，实际上还有其他方法
when we have limited data okay there is there are other ways actually
there is there are other ways actually that you know instead of getting the map
您知道而不是得到地图估算值，可能有人对此感兴趣
that you know instead of getting the map estimate somebody may be interested to
estimate somebody may be interested to get samples of actions II instead and I
取而代之的是行动II的样本，我想如果有时间我会来的
get samples of actions II instead and I think if I have time I'm going to come
think if I have time I'm going to come back to that because has implications in
回到这一点，因为对机器人技术和
back to that because has implications in the lots of applications in robotics and
the lots of applications in robotics and animation things that use particle
专门使用粒子过滤器进行动画操作的动画对象
animation things that use particle filter specially to operate with okay
对，所以今天我得到了马戏团小丑奥林匹克评论或
right so today I have been given a circus clown Olympic review or the
circus clown Olympic review or the message passing without using actually
消息传递而不实际使用它是科学物理的传播
message passing without using actually the propagation it is science physical
the propagation it is science physical science is you know prediction of
科学是您知道的关于气候是否存在的预测
science is you know prediction of whether climate whatever this is have
whether climate whatever this is have problems that you need on each of them
您每个人都需要的问题，所以我需要跨州访问，所以这是
problems that you need on each of them so I need to interstate so this is
so I need to interstate so this is what's called the filtering distribution
所谓的过滤分布
what's called the filtering distribution so the anticipate that the filtering
so the anticipate that the filtering distribution would be noisy you won't be
分布会很嘈杂，您将无法精确估算，因为不知何故
distribution would be noisy you won't be able estimated precisely because somehow
able estimated precisely because somehow you just got some measurements on the
您刚刚对案例进行了一些测量，您知道您不会
you just got some measurements on the case ago you know you're not going to
case ago you know you're not going to give the best estimates for this G of T
给出T的G的最佳估计，因此期望此滤波分布能够
give the best estimates for this G of T so expect this filtering distribution to
so expect this filtering distribution to be noise the smoothing distribution
是噪声，实际上是我们给它定义的平滑分布
be noise the smoothing distribution which we actually gives it to define
which we actually gives it to define this gamma messages okay is the
这个伽马信息好了，是计算给定的小T的条件
this gamma messages okay is the condition to compute the little T given
condition to compute the little T given all the data back to capital T this is
所有返回资本T的数据都是平滑分布，因此
all the data back to capital T this is the smoothing distribution so
the smoothing distribution so effectively you use future data to do
有效地使用将来的数据在更早的时间进行估算，以便您知道
effectively you use future data to do estimation at earlier times so you know
estimation at earlier times so you know this is an effective organization if you
这是一个有效的组织，如果您喜欢在此目的地上的话，那么
this is an effective organization if you like on the on on this destination so
like on the on on this destination so you expect this distribution to be where
您期望此分布比现在的分布更适合母亲
you expect this distribution to be where is mother than this distribution now
is mother than this distribution now this
这
并有奢侈地做，并在您想先做的任何时候给您估计
is mother than this distribution now this
and have the luxury to do and give estimation as anytime you want to first
并有奢侈地做，并在您想先做的任何时候给您估计
estimation as anytime you want to first you say yes to me now so that's the best
您现在对我说是，这是您可以做的最好的事情，所以这非常
you say yes to me now so that's the best you can do okay so this is very much
you can do okay so this is very much related sort of if you are going to do
相关的问题，如果你要做一个反问题，也许这是更多
related sort of if you are going to do an inverse problem maybe this is more
an inverse problem maybe this is more related but if you do online estimation
相关，但如果您进行在线估算，则想知道在哪里导航
related but if you do online estimation you want to know where to navigate about
you want to know where to navigate about let you know you need to know the faith
让您知道您需要一直了解信仰圣经，因此这是
let you know you need to know the faith Testament all the time so this is the
Testament all the time so this is the distribution interplay with obviously
显然，您知道可以进行一些平滑处理
distribution interplay with obviously you know you can do some smoothing not
you know you can do some smoothing not that the state feedback of say P minus L
如果说P减去L的状态反馈，那么这是固定的更大的东西，如果
that the state feedback of say P minus L so this is the fixed large more thing if
so this is the fixed large more thing if you pixel so maybe at this time you can
您的像素，所以也许此时您可以获取先前估计的营养
you pixel so maybe at this time you can have the nutrient the previous estimates
have the nutrient the previous estimates all right this is this fixed large house
好吧，这是这座固定的大房子，你无能为力
all right this is this fixed large house nothing you can do predictions of what
nothing you can do predictions of what the state is going to be next
状态将是下一个好吧，所以这就是这里
the state is going to be next all right so this is and here the simple
all right so this is and here the simple calculation on how using the time of the
计算如何使用时间P的时间实际比
calculation on how using the time of the time P to actually go further than
time P to actually go further than calculate the speed T steps ahead and
计算前进的速度T现在，这实际上是唯一
calculate the speed T steps ahead and now this is actually the only thing that
now this is actually the only thing that you need to know to do this calculation
您需要知道执行此计算就是要知道此过滤分布
you need to know to do this calculation is to know this filtering distribution
is to know this filtering distribution which we will compute okay that's the
我们将计算确定，这是过滤分布并使用基本
which we will compute okay that's the filtering distribution and using basic
filtering distribution and using basic laws of probability the two additional
概率定律即将到来的另外两件事是
laws of probability the two additional things that are coming is the
things that are coming is the transitions from T to T plus 1 and Tim
从T到T加1的转换和Tim加1到T加2的转换实际上可以设置
transitions from T to T plus 1 and Tim plus 1 to T plus 2 you can actually set
plus 1 to T plus 2 you can actually set the algebra
代数确定，您知道确实存在的风险
the algebra ok the risk you know there is really
ok the risk you know there is really nothing here so it's basically this
这里什么都没有，所以基本上是使用
nothing here so it's basically this calculation for dimensionalize with
calculation for dimensionalize with respect to DT and DT plus 1 so you can
尊重DT和DT加号1，这样您就可以雀巢未来，但是您不会
respect to DT and DT plus 1 so you can Nestle the future right but you do not
Nestle the future right but you do not need to now again with the filtering
现在需要再次使用时间T处的过滤分布
need to now again with the filtering distribution at time T
正确的东西，实际上您看不到书中有什么，但是它是
right and something that actually you don't see what's in books but it is
don't see what's in books but it is essential as you collect date and time
在收集日期和时间时必不可少，您可能想问问自己好吗
essential as you collect date and time you may want to ask yourself okay a
you may want to ask yourself okay a collected date of the time T what is the
时间T的收集日期，观察到某些需求的概率是多少？
collected date of the time T what is the probability of observing some need a
probability of observing some need a part time T plus eight all right so you
兼职T加8没事，所以您可以把这辆出租汽车算作是对的
part time T plus eight all right so you can figure this rental car as a right
can figure this rental car as a right but based on the knowledge that you have
但根据您知道您有时间T的知识，它告诉您
but based on the knowledge that you have up to time T it tells you the
up to time T it tells you the probability of observing beta X at time
在时间T加h观测到βX的概率，所以这就是所谓的a
probability of observing beta X at time T plus h so this is what is called a
T plus h so this is what is called a posterior predictive dance that they are
后预测舞蹈，他们是正确的，区别主要来自
posterior predictive dance that they are right and the difference basically from
right and the difference basically from what we did here is here we are
我们在这里所做的是在这里，我们预测在这里受到攻击的国家是
what we did here is here we are predicting the state attacked here were
predicting the state attacked here were predicting the observations have these
预测观测值具有这些分布，您可以在此处看到
predicting the observations have these distributions you see here of this
distributions you see here of this picture there is very fundamental I mean
图片是非常基本的，我的意思是，如果这就是为什么我要这样做，
picture there is very fundamental I mean if that's why I'm trying to do this as
if that's why I'm trying to do this as elementary as possible because if you
最基本的，因为如果您从事与
elementary as possible because if you work on anything that has to do with
work on anything that has to do with mental and dynamics which is it it
心理和动力学是什么，这与技术无关紧要
mental and dynamics which is it it doesn't matter what the technique is if
doesn't matter what the technique is if it's an hmm if it is a mechanic's
这是一个嗯，如果它是机械师的宇宙的概率
it's an hmm if it is a mechanic's probabilities of the universe of the
probabilities of the universe of the whole or something whatever was in
全部或今天未使用的东西都可以
whole or something whatever was in unused today this is it okay
unused today this is it okay so you need to know this idea now that's
所以你现在需要知道这个主意，而不是问题和海拔
so you need to know this idea now that's not the problems and the elevation
not the problems and the elevation problems that they're a little more
他们在工作中有些困难的问题
problems that they're a little more complicated to do work where some we
complicated to do work where some we have discussed right when I give you say
当我给您很好地介绍维特比简介时，我们已经进行了正确的讨论
have discussed right when I give you say well an introduction to the Viterbi
well an introduction to the Viterbi algorithm what does the Viterbi
算法维特比算法是什么
algorithm what does the Viterbi algorithm
我们告诉算法什么
what was that we tell the algorithm
你知道我们花了半个小时，你们忘了
you know we spent half an hour on it and you guys forgot about
而且我敢肯定有人会听见异象，但有些可信的系统却没有
and I'm sure somebody listens the vision sees some believable systems don't
sees some believable systems don't remember what was the Viterbi algorithm
记住什么是维特比算法，什么不是，所以有点伤害了你
remember what was the Viterbi algorithm what is not so what was a bit hurt you
所以这是最有效的部分
so it was the most effective part right
考虑到一些阻力，他说的最有可能看到的是
given some of the resistance exhaust it is that what he said the most likely saw
is that what he said the most likely saw this many this is the path from Z of Z
在给定的情况下，这就是从Z的Z到1到大写T的路径。
this many this is the path from Z of Z from 1 to capital T given the
from 1 to capital T given the observation of x1 city ok so the basic
观察x1城市好吧，所以基本无穷大，尤其是如果
observation of x1 city ok so the basic infinite especially if the states of
infinite especially if the states of every time is the bigger number alright
每次都是更大的数字，所以这说明我们基本上是在最大化
every time is the bigger number alright so this says we're maximizing basically
so this says we're maximizing basically the posterior but in the be turbulent if
后部，但是如果我们真的很感兴趣，则在湍流中定义这是
the posterior but in the be turbulent if we were really interested define this is
we were really interested define this is not what the maximum joint distribution
不是所有这些的最大联合分布，而是找到我们的
not what the maximum joint distribution all those this was but to find what our
all those this was but to find what our resist what is the path that maximizes
抵制什么是使力场分布最大化的路径，现在您
resist what is the path that maximizes this force field distribution now you
this force field distribution now you know again it's the true thick to give
再次知道这是给你做作业的真正动力，
know again it's the true thick to give you a homework on this to drive you not
you a homework on this to drive you not so you can learn something but the idea
所以你可以学到一些东西，但是这里的想法不是很稳健
so you can learn something but the idea here is this is not a very robust
here is this is not a very robust calculation and sometimes if you want
计算，有时如果您愿意的话，可能会很高兴
calculation and sometimes if you want this you may be happy if you actually go
this you may be happy if you actually go from the posterior or something taking
从后方或其他可能需要估算的力量
from the posterior or something taking you may want to estimate strong force
you may want to estimate strong force all right so it's a very substantial
好吧，这是一个非常实质性的问题，我们以
all right so it's a very substantial problem and we covered this idea with
problem and we covered this idea with using sequence some of the cargo methods
在秋天的过程中使用顺序的一些货运方法，所以如果
using sequence some of the cargo methods in the course in in the fall so if
in the course in in the fall so if anybody wants to read more details on
任何人都想使用顺序阅读更多有关此类问题的详细信息
anybody wants to read more details on this type of problems using sequential
this type of problems using sequential Montecarlo used to look up then this is
蒙特卡洛（Montecarlo）过去常常抬头，这不是我强调的，这不是特别
Montecarlo used to look up then this is not I emphasize this is not particular
not I emphasize this is not particular to this fast if you do any problem where
如果您有任何问题要输入数据，那么可以快到这些
to this fast if you do any problem where you have data coming in right these are
you have data coming in right these are fundamental problems there is no way you
基本问题，没有办法可以逃脱，这是在我们任何
fundamental problems there is no way you can escape from this ok it's in our any
can escape from this ok it's in our any character in computer science and
在计算机科学和化学工程中的物理特性
character in computer science and physics in chemistry in engineering this
physics in chemistry in engineering this is a very sensitive problem to be able
能够从后部采样是一个非常敏感的问题，这
is a very sensitive problem to be able sample from the posterior ok this
sample from the posterior ok this all right you need to play from the
您需要从证据中发挥所有作用，以最大程度地利用证据
all right you need to play from the evidence to maximize the evidence with
evidence to maximize the evidence with respect to the parameters this is how at
相对于参数，这就是一天结束时甚至EMR的结果
respect to the parameters this is how at the end of the day even the EMR which
the end of the day even the EMR which works but this calculation is not what
可以，但是这种计算不是您需要做的，我们仍然会做
works but this calculation is not what you need to do and we would still what
you need to do and we would still what if you do message passing actually you
如果您实际上进行消息传递，则可以始终使用线性计算
if you do message passing actually you can calculate this always with linear
can calculate this always with linear cost on the length of the chain in a
使用前进和后退以非常琐碎的方式花费在链的长度上
cost on the length of the chain in a very trivial fashion using forward and
very trivial fashion using forward and backward messaging all right so this is
可以向后传送消息，所以这是一张显示不同问题的图片
backward messaging all right so this is a picture showing the different problems
a picture showing the different problems alright are you sure we did and this is
好吧，您确定我们做了吗，这又是一个示例，它在注释中
alright are you sure we did and this is an example again it's in the notes to
an example again it's in the notes to tell you how the different resolution
告诉你我不会经历的不同分辨率，所以让我
tell you how the different resolution I'm not gonna go through that so let me
I'm not gonna go through that so let me keep going and going all right right I
一直走下去，没事吧，我有消息解析算法，
keep going and going all right right I have the message parsing algorithms that
have the message parsing algorithms that you need in the context of the e/m
您需要在e / m算法的上下文中具有更好的关系
you need in the context of the e/m algorithm to have better relations
algorithm to have better relations without using after the propagation none
在传播之后不使用上面的任何一个，因为我们已经完成了所有
without using after the propagation none of the above because we have done all of
of the above because we have done all of this i'd always using the simple rules
这就是我总是使用概率的简单规则，我想
this i'd always using the simple rules of probability and i want to
没有什么新的压缩方式，因此您在精神上不需要
there's nothing new the compressions are so you mentally you don't need to
so you mentally you don't need to complicate them for this problem to get
使这个问题复杂化以获得此结果，您可以获得很多
complicate them for this problem to get this results you can get them with a lot
this results you can get them with a lot of ability and you may ask me then why
能力，你可能会问我为什么信仰传播以及所有这些
of ability and you may ask me then why did belief propagation and all of these
did belief propagation and all of these things on junction 3 well because not
3号交汇处的东西很好，因为不是所有东西都没有锁住更多
things on junction 3 well because not everything is it didn't lock up more
everything is it didn't lock up more than in life well the pumps are much
比起生活，水泵要复杂得多。
than in life well the pumps are much more complicated right you know can be
more complicated right you know can be anything and you know that is not a tree
任何东西，你知道那不是一棵树，你将无法使用此递归
anything and you know that is not a tree you won't be able to use this recursive
you won't be able to use this recursive techniques you have to use belief
您必须使用置信传播结点树的技术，但是
techniques you have to use belief propagation Junction tree however it's
propagation Junction tree however it's as we discussed okay but the end that
正如我们讨论的那样，但是最后就像我们覆盖的国家太空水一样
as we discussed okay but the end that like the state space water we covered
like the state space water we covered next week I'll sort of the essential
下周，我将介绍它们的基本要素，并且我想确保
next week I'll sort of the essential element of them and I want to be sure
element of them and I want to be sure that can work to actually notice it okay
可以实际注意到它，所以很多计算基本上
that can work to actually notice it okay so lots of calculations basically to
so lots of calculations basically to convey to themselves that they
向自己传达他们了解正在使用的内容
convey to themselves that they understand what's going on using
understand what's going on using absolutely nothing else but dissipation
除了隐藏的马尔可夫的消散和独立性外，别无其他
absolutely nothing else but dissipation and independence for the hidden Markov
and independence for the hidden Markov model okay so what you want is I want to
模型好，所以您想要的是我想要完成的动漫内容，这意味着
model okay so what you want is I want to complete with anime means this the
complete with anime means this the problem intensity given the data time T
给定数据时间T的问题强度，我们称其为滤波
problem intensity given the data time T and we call this the filtering
and we call this the filtering distribution okay so in two steps
分布好，所以分两步好，所以我们假设
distribution okay so in two steps okay so we're going to assume that this
okay so we're going to assume that this is going to be recursive calculation is
将是递归计算将是正向计算
is going to be recursive calculation is going to be a forward calculation which
going to be a forward calculation which means I am going to assume that somehow
意味着我将假设我以某种方式知道时间的这种内容分布
means I am going to assume that somehow I know this content distribution of time
I know this content distribution of time t minus one okay so this distribution
t减去一好，所以我们在这里看到的分布
t minus one okay so this distribution that we see here
无论如何，所以计划是继续进行计算，我们只剩下两个步骤，所以第一步
anyway so the plan is to compute on and we're leaving two steps so the first
we're leaving two steps so the first step is I am going to calculate the
步骤是我要计算ZP的预测分布
step is I am going to calculate the predictive distribution of Z P which is
predictive distribution of Z P which is one step ahead give it back up to ten
向前走一步，最多可退十减一
one step ahead give it back up to ten minus one
minus one I mean this is you can enter this
我的意思是，这是您可以输入这个方程式，您不会告诉我
I mean this is you can enter this equation and you're not gonna tell me
equation and you're not gonna tell me you don't understand from 40k right so I
您从40k处无法理解，所以我需要计算等于j的城市
you don't understand from 40k right so I need to calculate this city equal to j
need to calculate this city equal to j given extra 1 to t minus 1 and I have
给定额外的1到t减去1，我这样做是因为
given extra 1 to t minus 1 and I have that I do this as the probability of
that I do this as the probability of city - one being I given the date up to
城市-我给的日期是t减去1，然后是CP的概率
city - one being I given the date up to t minus 1 and then the probability of CP
t minus 1 and then the probability of CP given 60 minus 1 the shipping for a
给定60减1，对于一个浸信会荒谬的人，我介绍了ZT减
given 60 minus 1 the shipping for a Baptist ridiculous I introduced ZT minus
Baptist ridiculous I introduced ZT minus 1 inside there so I perform a city minus
里面有1个，所以我执行的城市为负1和负J
1 inside there so I perform a city minus 1 and minus J okay okay
1 and minus J okay okay you need some country no okay all right
您需要某个国家/地区，好的，那很好，所以我们假设我们
you need some country no okay all right so that's one okay so we we assume we
so that's one okay so we we assume we know things up to two minus one we know
知道最多2减一的事情，我们知道这一点，所以我们可以在时间上领先一步
know things up to two minus one we know this so we can go one step ahead in time
this so we can go one step ahead in time T and find city I'm going to compute
找城市，我将计算风险，并探索不同的城市
T and find city I'm going to compute risk and I'm exploring the different
risk and I'm exploring the different notations in the literature basically
文献中的记号基本上不要混淆，它们全都给了您
notations in the literature basically don't get confused they all give you the
don't get confused they all give you the same answers at the end of the day so we
在一天结束时有相同的答案，所以我们要计算这个，这是
same answers at the end of the day so we want to compute this and this is this is
want to compute this and this is this is what we have used it exactly like this
我们使用它的方式与此完全一样，但在此基础上有所不同
what we have used it exactly like this in with some difference based on this
in with some difference based on this normalization factor the probability of
归一化因子数据的概率还可以，这种分布是我的
normalization factor the probability of the data okay this distribution to be my
the data okay this distribution to be my optimistic I'll give it a name J okay so
乐观的我给它起个名字J好吧，所以我1/2 T是X 1到t减去1以及XT全部
optimistic I'll give it a name J okay so I 1/2 T is X 1 to t minus 1 and XT all
I 1/2 T is X 1 to t minus 1 and XT all right and I say this looks ball should
是的，我说这看起来不应该无聊，除非X的X
right and I say this looks ball should not be bored okay all right unless X of
not be bored okay all right unless X of course is a multi-variant volleyball
那里当然是多元排球
course is a multi-variant volleyball there okay
there okay so what you write down from here to
所以基本上当我完成时，您从这里写下的内容
so what you write down from here to there so basically when I have done by
there so basically when I have done by using a factory sent obey this rule if
如果您愿意，或者使用我记得的概率，使用发送给工厂的工厂服从该规则
using a factory sent obey this rule if you like or the probabilities I remember
you like or the probabilities I remember sixth eighth to the left and I move a
左边第六个第八，我移动归一化
sixth eighth to the left and I move a normalization
社区，但仍有条件与您投资，这是有毒的
communities but conditions still investing with you know toxic this is is
investing with you know toxic this is is you know because what distribution is
您知道，因为这是什么分布，这是我们计算出的分布，
you know because what distribution is this is the distribution we computed and
this is the distribution we computed and what distribution is risk
您从未使用过XP会导致什么分布风险？
what distribution is risk you never does XP the based on the
you never does XP the based on the previous measurements if I know the
如果我知道时间T耗散的强度是您，则可以进行先前的测量
previous measurements if I know the strength of time T dissipation is you
strength of time T dissipation is you know the state the kind of patient I'm
知道状态我会提示的病人好吗，所以另一个消息是
know the state the kind of patient I'm tips okay so the other message which is
tips okay so the other message which is this is written as observation value
这被写成我们知道还可以并标准化的观测值
this is written as observation value which we know okay and the normalization
which we know okay and the normalization factor that we live here is that there
我们住在这里的一个因素是，他们给了媒体效果X 1 2 3
factor that we live here is that there are media effects they given X 1 2 3
are media effects they given X 1 2 3 minus 1 and this way the normalization
减1，这样归一化因子就是如果您将所有这些都考虑在内
minus 1 and this way the normalization factor is if you take all of this
factor is if you take all of this alright and you sign for the possible
好吧，那么您基本上就签署了Z的可能值
alright and you sign for the possible values of Z so basically if you take
values of Z so basically if you take this distribution there and you
在那里存在该分布，并且您相对于Z对其进行归一化
this distribution there and you normalize it with respect to Z you get
normalize it with respect to Z you get the GT and it looks shelter for useless
GT，它看起来可以为无用的计算提供庇护，DT的精湛之处在于
the GT and it looks shelter for useless calculation this DT virtuosity would be
calculation this DT virtuosity would be essential because you will give us a
必不可少，因为您将为我们快速计算证据，但是
essential because you will give us a rapid calculation of the evidence but is
rapid calculation of the evidence but is used everywhere in Mesilla okay message
在Mesilla好的消息中到处使用，这就是大致定义的方式
used everywhere in Mesilla okay message and this is the way that roughly defines
and this is the way that roughly defines it as the poster of city given date up
它作为指定城市的发布者，其日期可多达20个，因此句子可以知道
it as the poster of city given date up to 20 so sentences but can know their
to 20 so sentences but can know their papers and many other offers they
论文和许多其他提议，他们将Alpha质量定义为
papers and many other offers they defined the Alpha masses not as the
defined the Alpha masses not as the posterior of ZT given this data but
给定此数据但不是联合的ZT的后部
posterior of ZT given this data but isn't joint
isn't joint and papers inside my notes if not
和我笔记中的文件（如果未注明）表示该后部还好
and papers inside my notes if not indicate this one as the posterior okay
x1到XP，并在舞台上结束，但这是第一个状态相同的视频
x1 to XP and ending on stage but this is the first video to have the state equal
the first video to have the state equal to J given all the observations there
给J那里的所有观察都更快，同样的事情还可以
to J given all the observations there faster the same thing okay
faster the same thing okay but again is when you do calculations to
但是同样是当您进行计算以将其定义得很远时，所以我们
but again is when you do calculations to define it very distant and and so we
define it very distant and and so we don't have any mistakes what I chose
没有任何错误，我选择了对不起
don't have any mistakes what I chose sorry
sorry the line senescence defined as this
定义为该滤波后验分布的线衰老是
the line senescence defined as this filtering posterior distribution is the
filtering posterior distribution is the product of the observation model times
观察模型的乘积乘以这一预测步骤
product of the observation model times this predictive one step ahead
this predictive one step ahead distribution where this one step ahead
如此向前迈出的一步是这样写的：
distribution where this one step ahead the tradition was written like that and
the tradition was written like that and I can tell you that it's there if you
我可以告诉你，如果您想提供此功能，它就在那里
I can tell you that it's there if you want to provision this
want to provision this it's a one-line calculation so a music
这是单行计算，因此本书中的音乐符号可以将他划分为
it's a one-line calculation so a music notation from at this book to divide he
notation from at this book to divide he divides me the transition matrix notice
给我除数转换矩阵注意一个叹息和观察模型
divides me the transition matrix notice a capital sigh and the observation model
a capital sigh and the observation model of the state text a XD Givens DJ is DT
XD Givens DJ的状态文本的DT等于J，只要J被任命者稍感叹
of the state text a XD Givens DJ is DT equal to J as little sigh of J appointee
equal to J as little sigh of J appointee and
和
好的，所以当我执行此组合时，每个矩阵的乘积是一个矩阵乘以一个向量
equal to J as little sigh of J appointee and
okay so when I do this combination is a matrix times a vector for each of the
好的，所以当我执行此组合时，每个矩阵的乘积是一个矩阵乘以一个向量
matrix times a vector for each of the stage I guess I get this vector and what
我猜我得到这个向量，这是什么
stage I guess I get this vector and what is this
好的，这意味着你需要做的很好
okay which means you need to be done okay
推导中的归一化权是给定的概率
the normalization right in the derivation here is the probability given
derivation here is the probability given all the previous data this is nice you
以前的所有数据都很不错，您知道为什么要归一化
all the previous data this is nice you know why because of this normalization
know why because of this normalization factor from time 1 to capital P it will
从时间1到大写P的因数，它实际上将为您提供从1到
factor from time 1 to capital P it will give you actually the evidence from 1 to
give you actually the evidence from 1 to capital T so the evidence basically is
大写T，所以证据基本上是所有法线的总和
capital T so the evidence basically is the summation of all of the normal is
the summation of all of the normal is the launch of the organization factors
正常化时您将获得的组织因素的启动
the launch of the organization factors that you will get when you normalize
that you will get when you normalize this outlet is probability okay so so
这个出口是可以的，所以另一个基本上是你知道的
this outlet is probability okay so so the other one is basically you know
the other one is basically you know obviously you have to start the
显然，您必须启动该公式的算法单元
obviously you have to start the algorithm units that formula
algorithm units that formula message-passing you have to calculate
传递消息，您必须计算Alpha度量和归一化
message-passing you have to calculate the Alpha measures and the normalization
the Alpha measures and the normalization factor step one and then basically you
因子第一步，然后基本上您就可以进行这种乘法
factor step one and then basically you do this multiplication this kind of our
do this multiplication this kind of our product you normalize to get the
您归一化的产品以获得归一化GT和消息alpha T
product you normalize to get the normalization GT and the message alpha T
normalization GT and the message alpha T and if you want find the evidence
如果您想找到证据，基本上可以将所有
and if you want find the evidence basically you take the sum of all the
basically you take the sum of all the logs of cities and as the evidence and
城市的日志，并作为证据和结果
logs of cities and as the evidence and results am
家庭的定义并没有什么不同，因为它是如此个性化
definition of family it doesn't make a difference because it's so personal you
difference because it's so personal you know going to sound to our answer if
知道会听起来像我们的答案，如果这可以使他们规范化，那么如果您
know going to sound to our answer if this can normalize them and so if you
this can normalize them and so if you only think you're fine definition versus
只觉得自己和其他人比较好
only think you're fine definition versus the other
the other either the normalization factor will
归一化因素将影响到所有人，而您
either the normalization factor will come to be on everyone and you
come to be on everyone and you contradict okay so you don't have to
矛盾好，所以您不必担心患者的年龄，因为
contradict okay so you don't have to worry about the patient's years because
worry about the patient's years because they're at the end of the day equivalent
他们一天结束时
如果我能以明确的形式给出，那是计算权，可以确保完成
worry about the patient's years because they're at the end of the day equivalent
if I can give in in explicit form it's a calculation right for sure to complete
如果我能以明确的形式给出，那是计算权，可以确保完成
calculation right for sure to complete the message a 12-time think you need to
消息12次认为您需要知道xt减1的问题，并且
the message a 12-time think you need to know the matter of x t minus 1 and
know the matter of x t minus 1 and effectively obviously you need to
有效地，显然，您需要通过过渡来推进这一点
effectively obviously you need to advance this with the transition
advance this with the transition probability plus the observation model
概率加上观察模型，所以这是一个比喻
probability plus the observation model and so so it's a parable más despacio
and so so it's a parable más despacio now there's masses past week and even
现在有群众过去一周，甚至当我们做了交界处树
now there's masses past week and even when we did the junction tree
when we did the junction tree implementation for the hmm I told you
我告诉你他们正在讨论的HMM的实现更多
implementation for the hmm I told you that they're discussing is more
that they're discussing is more important than the message passing so
比传递的信息重要，所以我要从一个不祥的话题开始
important than the message passing so I'm gonna start with an ominous is
I'm gonna start with an ominous is fasting but I'll be trying to make the
禁食，但考虑到
fasting but I'll be trying to make the posterior of City given what type of
posterior of City given what type of distribution then is this is this a
分布然后是这是一个过滤分布这是什么
distribution then is this is this a filtering distribution what is this is a
filtering distribution what is this is a smoothing distribution so the nominal
平滑分布，因此标称桅杆现在是因为该能力已知
smoothing distribution so the nominal mast is now because the ability know
mast is now because the ability know what reduces
什么减少
我要去那里发生的事情，所以我要去，所以我有x的P
mast is now because the ability know what reduces
I am going to what's going out there so I am going to so I have P of x1 the
我要去那里发生的事情，所以我要去，所以我有x的P
I am going to so I have P of x1 the capital T given the different sphere of
大写字母T给出了CT的不同领域，现在我正在使用
capital T given the different sphere of CT and now a righty I am using the
CT and now a righty I am using the observations T plus 1 to capital
观测值T加1等于大写
这是独立
CT and now a righty I am using the observations T plus 1 to capital
this is independence
没关系，所以这是炼金术士吗？
it doesn't matter so this is the alchemist isn't it remember messages the
alchemist isn't it remember messages the provision of you
您在T时刻的占有情况和特定状态
provision of you occupy and um given state at time T
occupy and um given state at time T right so that's the Alpha message and
对，所以这就是Alpha信息，这就是我们所说的已知信息
right so that's the Alpha message and what is this this is what we call known
what is this this is what we call known ago the bitter message is knowing that I
以前，这条痛苦的消息是知道我从等于P的20 P开始
ago the bitter message is knowing that I start at twenty P equal to J let's say
start at twenty P equal to J let's say what's the preferred video that will
观看Dave XT加1到XT的首选视频是什么？
what's the preferred video that will observe Dave XT plus 1 to X T okay
observe Dave XT plus 1 to X T okay that's the bigger message so you can see
这是更大的信息，所以您可以看到现在有一​​个系统，任何人
that's the bigger message so you can see that there are now a system where anyone
that there are now a system where anyone interested is the product of the I'll
感兴趣的是我的产品，我将再次传达已标准化的消息
interested is the product of the I'll convey the message normalized okay again
然后使用此公式计算ZT的范围，您平均知道8
and then use this formula to compute the realm of ZT you know an average of eight
realm of ZT you know an average of eight GT is the most easy thing to complete
GT是最容易完成的事情，因为归根结底，
GT is the most easy thing to complete because at the end of the day in the my
because at the end of the day in the my well at least you care about the gamma
好吧，至少您关心的是伽玛消息，我们不在乎更大的消息
well at least you care about the gamma messages we don't care about the bigger
messages we don't care about the bigger messages but you know one way or another
消息，但您知道一种或另一种计算方法将是相似的
messages but you know one way or another the computation approach will be similar
the computation approach will be similar violence so when you complete this
暴力，因此当您完成这种不同的营销时，可以从中获利
violence so when you complete this different marketing take the profits of
different marketing take the profits of each thing to get this or if you come up
每件事都会得到这个，或者如果您想出关于伽玛城市更新的规定
each thing to get this or if you come up with regulation for gamma city updates
with regulation for gamma city updates so to calculate the beta messages at t
因此，要计算t减去1时的beta消息，基本上是较大的
so to calculate the beta messages at t minus one is basically the bigger
minus one is basically the bigger message supplying P times the transition
消息提供P乘以过渡矩阵，提供G乘以
message supplying P times the transition matrix provide the G times the
matrix provide the G times the observation model at time T and you
在时间T的观测模型，您代表J阶段的所有权利，这是
observation model at time T and you stand for all stage J right and this
stand for all stage J right and this this is the
这是关键点是t减一，然后
this is the the point is t minus one and the
the point is t minus one and the delicious actually
美味实际上是微不足道的，如果您要编程
delicious actually trivial and if you want to program the
trivial and if you want to program the bigger message literally what you notice
从字面上看，您看到的更大的信息是您之间从来没有足够的产品
bigger message literally what you notice you never have enough product between
you never have enough product between the observer and model and the message
观察者和模型以及消息beta时间T，然后一旦找到
the observer and model and the message beta time T and then once you've found
beta time T and then once you've found that vector we multiply the proposition
该向量我们将命题字母I乘以而没有新向量，您得到
that vector we multiply the proposition letters I without new vector and you get
letters I without new vector and you get the message because P minus 1 and again
该消息是因为P减去1，然后您再说一次，如果您定义本质位
the message because P minus 1 and again you say if you define the bit of essence
you say if you define the bit of essence or the Alpha masters in a different way
或以其他方式使用Alpha大师，这可能会成为参考
or the Alpha masters in a different way this may come to make reference right
this may come to make reference right but the normalization factor you can
但是之后您可以击败的归一化因素就是为什么我将
but the normalization factor you can beat afterwards that's why I put a
beat afterwards that's why I put a proportionality condition there so that
那里的比例条件，所以这适用于任何
proportionality condition there so that this is applicable to whatever
this is applicable to whatever definitions used for the outcome
结果的定义可以衡量，所以他不会
definitions used for the outcome measures okay so so he doesn't make
measures okay so so he doesn't make alright if you do this update then at
好吧，如果您执行此更新，则在此时完成所有
alright if you do this update then at this time when you finish going all the
this time when you finish going all the way backwards you can multiply the often
向后退，您可以乘以通常更大的消息，即时间T和
way backwards you can multiply the often bigger message that it's time T and this
bigger message that it's time T and this will give me the gamma masters this is
会给我伽玛大师的机会这是我们开始时的初始条件
will give me the gamma masters this is the initial condition we started with a
the initial condition we started with a bit of Masters of Terror at the end
最后一点恐怖大师基本上等于1让我看看我是否
bit of Masters of Terror at the end basically equal to 1 let me see if I
basically equal to 1 let me see if I have a date for gamma
有个约会
我的伽玛是什么
basically equal to 1 let me see if I have a date for gamma
what is my gamma
你看到拉玛森文员
you see rammasun Clerk
好吧，这是我要指向狡猾的地方，所以我将继续单击鼠标右键，但在
okay so it's I'm pointing to sly so I'm going to keep clicking all right but at
going to keep clicking all right but at least we got one way we got one way to
至少我们有一种方法来计算这些伽玛混乱
least we got one way we got one way to compute these gamma messes by
compute these gamma messes by multiplying the Alpha and the beta
可以将Alpha和Beta信息相乘，如果您要查找
multiplying the Alpha and the beta messages okay and if you want to find
messages okay and if you want to find that away with the alpha beta resistant
有了alpha beta抗性，我们就做到了这一点，而且效果很好
that away with the alpha beta resistant we did this really well as well look at
we did this really well as well look at this equation right
如果此紫色图像已归一化，则该方程式正确
this equation right if this purple images have normalized
if this purple images have normalized and and the definition that I have here
以及我在这里的定义被归一化，您总结为个人
and and the definition that I have here are normalized and you sum for personal
are normalized and you sum for personal values of this to GT this posterior
此GT的后验概率总和为1，因此实际上
values of this to GT this posterior probabilities will sum to 1 so actually
probabilities will sum to 1 so actually from this equation at any node P you can
从任何节点P的该方程式中，您可以通过以下步骤计算证据：
from this equation at any node P you can calculate the evidence by standing on
calculate the evidence by standing on possible values of the city by
通过将主日Alpha和相乘得出城市的可能值
possible values of the city by multiplying the master day alpha and
multiplying the master day alpha and beta okay
测试版还可以，实际上，该公式甚至可以
beta okay and in actually this formula can even
and in actually this formula can even look more trivial if you select there's
如果您选择没有P作为您知道的大写字母T，看起来会更琐碎
look more trivial if you select there's no P to be the capital you know T you
no P to be the capital you know T you know why how is this a question going to
知道为什么这是一个简单的问题，如果我们将其应用于
know why how is this a question going to be simplified if we apply to this is for
be simplified if we apply to this is for a multi to be total time taken to
资本T花费的总时间的倍数
a multi to be total time taken to capital T what the dissipation will be
capital T what the dissipation will be politically applied for T equal to
在政治上申请等于资本T的T你记得我在某个地方
politically applied for T equal to capital T you remember somewhere I
capital T you remember somewhere I mentioned something here
在这里提到了一些东西
当您初始化migga消息时，例如从它们开始，
capital T you remember somewhere I mentioned something here
when you initialize the migga messages like starting from them the messages of
当您初始化migga消息时，例如从它们开始，
like starting from them the messages of yourself is equal to one so effectively
你自己等于一个人，所以它可以有效地占据一个均匀的位置
yourself is equal to one so effectively it can occupy played this in an even
it can occupy played this in an even simpler way out there is no good day
更简单的方法是没有美好的一天，就像我们做的总结一样
simpler way out there is no good day will it look like we do the summation of
will it look like we do the summation of the MS is too long again that's it okay
MS又太长了，没关系
叹息一定有一个基本的可用精华素，你记得我们曾经有过
will it look like we do the summation of the MS is too long again that's it okay
sighs there must be a basic available essences potential you remember we had
叹息一定有一个基本的可用精华素，你记得我们曾经有过
essences potential you remember we had to complete this joint distribution of z
完成z PM zp加1的联合分布
to complete this joint distribution of z PM z p plus 1 the procedure given
PM z p plus 1 the procedure given observation choice there's nothing joint
观察选择没有联合分布，所以我们需要记住
observation choice there's nothing joint distribution so we needed remembering
distribution so we needed remembering the sufficient statistics that were
即将到来的足够统计量X-Alki J转换矩阵
the sufficient statistics that were coming X - Alki J the transition matrix
coming X - Alki J the transition matrix we need to find how many times will
我们需要找出多少次将陈述我和过渡状态，并且
we need to find how many times will state I and the transition say and that
state I and the transition say and that came out to be equal to this sufficient
出来等于这个足够的统计量，所以它的实际独立性
came out to be equal to this sufficient statistic so the actual independence it
statistic so the actual independence it comes out that the completeness the
得出在t减去1 t时从i到j的转变的完整性
comes out that the completeness the transition from i to j at t minus 1 t
transition from i to j at t minus 1 t what you need to do is the following
您需要做的是以下计算我所计算的要约消息
what you need to do is the following take the offer message computed i take
take the offer message computed i take the business is at P plus 1 computed J
业务为P加1的计算出的J乘以观察值
the business is at P plus 1 computed J multiplied with the observation more
multiplied with the observation more than P plus 1 computed a and multiplying
比P加1算出的a乘以位置乘以得固定，我会说和
than P plus 1 computed a and multiplying with the position let fix I'd say and
with the position let fix I'd say and actually if you remember with mastered
实际上，如果您还记得当我们想找到
actually if you remember with mastered passing right when we wanted to find the
passing right when we wanted to find the Joint Distribution between two two
两两晚之间的联合分发，您知道我们所做的就是
Joint Distribution between two two nights you know what we did is we took
nights you know what we did is we took that connects the two nights which is
连接这两个夜晚，这是事实的证明，然后我们
that connects the two nights which is this times the evidenced and then we
this times the evidenced and then we took the message coming one more than
收到的消息比剩下的先到达另一个音符多
took the message coming one more than the rest come to the other note first
the rest come to the other note first unless is counting authority on one
除非是在一个方向上指望权威，否则消息会及时到来
unless is counting authority on one direction the message is coming at time
direction the message is coming at time T so actually lists exactly the same
T所以当我们进行传播确定时，实际上列出了完全相同的方程式
T so actually lists exactly the same equations when we did the propagation ok
equations when we did the propagation ok so there's nothing it's just what is
所以什么都没有，那就是变化变小了
so there's nothing it's just what is know is that the variation is down in
know is that the variation is down in this rise with an elementary caution
在基本不谨慎的情况下，对这种上升情况不甚了解
this rise with an elementary caution without knowing very much about the
without knowing very much about the liberal foundation but all these a list
自由的基础，但所有这些日期列表仅适用于更改
liberal foundation but all these a list of dates are only applicable to change
of dates are only applicable to change and in this case the hidden Markov
在这种情况下，隐藏的马尔可夫模型
and in this case the hidden Markov models so
models so so if you want to complete this this
因此，如果您想完成此操作，请在工作室使用此衣服移动接头，然后
so if you want to complete this this clothes moving joint for studio and then
clothes moving joint for studio and then you have to form a matrix between this
你必须在这个标签和医生之间形成一个矩阵，所以基本上你
you have to form a matrix between this tab and doctor alright so basically you
tab and doctor alright so basically you know this is shorten shortage of
知道这是缩短业务短缺的原因，让我们在Beta版中说一下
know this is shorten shortage of business let's say here in beta what's
business let's say here in beta what's the vector okay metrics and then
向量正常指标，然后基本上就可以了，所以所有这些事情
the vector okay metrics and then basically okay so all of these things
basically okay so all of these things are ready to go if you guys want to
准备好了，如果你们想对此进行编程，又一次您知道您
are ready to go if you guys want to program this and again you know you
program this and again you know you don't like this and then whatever you
不喜欢这样，然后不管您有一个不错的级别化例程，
don't like this and then whatever you have a nice level ization routine and
have a nice level ization routine and you say now normalize so if you means
您说现在归一化，所以如果您表示知道它错过了
you say now normalize so if you means you know it miss this evidence from the
you know it miss this evidence from the bottom and it's better not have to
底部，最好不要打扰正确地保持所有
bottom and it's better not have to bother right keeping this track all the
bother right keeping this track all the time so you miss it you just come and be
时间，所以你想念它，你只是来成为正常的眼睛，实际上这会给
time so you miss it you just come and be normal eyes and actually that will give
normal eyes and actually that will give you immediately what that value of the
您立即发现证据的价值如何
you immediately what that value of the evidence all right
evidence all right so basically we use this to compute the
所以基本上我们用它来计算当我们
so basically we use this to compute the the sufficient statistics in in when we
the sufficient statistics in in when we did the you know the EMR growth since I
自从我提到维特比问题以来，您是否知道EMR的增长，所以让我
did the you know the EMR growth since I mentioned the Viterbi problem so let me
mentioned the Viterbi problem so let me go back to you
回到你身边
我要说的东西没有新意，我要重写你的问题
mentioned the Viterbi problem so let me go back to you
there is nothing new on what I'm going to say I'm gonna rewrite your question
我要说的东西没有新意，我要重写你的问题
to say I'm gonna rewrite your question again sure you guys can remember what we
再次确保你们能够记住我们所触摸的内容，因此我们有兴趣
again sure you guys can remember what we were touching so we're interested to
were touching so we're interested to find the maximum of the posterior focus
如果给了亚当所有数据，则找到后焦点的最大值
find the maximum of the posterior focus if Adam was given all the data but in
if Adam was given all the data but in particularly in the View tab you see
特别是在“查看”选项卡中，您会看到要找到被观察者或
particularly in the View tab you see which one is to find the observed or
which one is to find the observed or gives me that much
给我很多权利，这会占用时间或
gives me that much all right and this takes up its time or
all right and this takes up its time or many you know so this table is huge this
很多你知道，所以这张桌子很大，你不能去说给我
many you know so this table is huge this can you cannot go and say give me over
can you cannot go and say give me over stage and I would select one that much
阶段，我会选择一只后部那么多的老鼠
stage and I would select one that much mice the posterior
mice the posterior so now you need to find disease for
所以现在您需要找到要针对的疾病，这就是那里的论点
so now you need to find disease for which so that's the argument right there
which so that's the argument right there aren't much problem he'll find the
没什么大不了的，他会发现系统使这个后验最大化，我们
aren't much problem he'll find the system maximize this posterior and we
system maximize this posterior and we resent that
我认为最大化试剂是不满的
resent that maximizing reagent is I think it will
maximizing reagent is I think it will not give you a right answer so we need
没有给您正确的答案，因此我们需要最大化给定的时间步长
not give you a right answer so we need to maximize the given time step all
to maximize the given time step all right now edge weights
现在边缘权重
使用观察性滥用的任务旅行，过渡将
to maximize the given time step all right now edge weights
using the mission trip abused observationally and the transition will
使用观察性滥用的任务旅行，过渡将
observationally and the transition will be made this and especially much demise
要做到这一点，尤其是要消亡，我们必须把我的东西好起来，这是
be made this and especially much demise we must my stuff okay this is the
we must my stuff okay this is the stamping this is the probability of
盖章这是在您知道特定状态的概率
stamping this is the probability of being on you know a particular state one
being on you know a particular state one this is the observation model of state
这是状态一的观察模型，这是转移概率
this is the observation model of state one this is the transition probability
one this is the transition probability between two time steps and this is the
在两个时间步长之间，这是对时间T的观测，然后是
between two time steps and this is the observation of time T and then this is
observation of time T and then this is you move from here to there and then you
你从这里移到那里，然后你说民粹主义的最小方式是什么
you move from here to there and then you say what is the minimal way the populism
say what is the minimal way the populism in one maximal way basically and after
基本上以一种最大的方式，在德比部分之后，算法很简单
in one maximal way basically and after the Derby part the algorithm is simple
the Derby part the algorithm is simple dynamic programming algorithm gonna go
动态编程算法将直接走，实际上是一样的
dynamic programming algorithm gonna go directly which is actually the same
directly which is actually the same equation we have seen in this book
我们在本书中看到的等式Shalini占卜希望事情会
equation we have seen in this book shalini divination hopefully things will
shalini divination hopefully things will click and you remember whether the
单击，您会记住算法是否正确，然后告诉我这是什么
click and you remember whether the algorithms and tell me what that is
[音乐]
[Music]
-反身的关系，看那个定义，告诉我我们有什么
- reflexive relation looking at that definition and tell me what this we have
definition and tell me what this we have a question says good
一个问题说很好
回忆不是吗，因为那样的话你会不明白的，所以我们把我带走了
definition and tell me what this we have a question says good
memories don't it because then you will not understand okay so we took my square
回忆不是吗，因为那样的话你会不明白的，所以我们把我带走了
not understand okay so we took my square ended in 2-1
2-1结束
你知道味道，基本上给我最佳的味道
not understand okay so we took my square ended in 2-1
you know the taste and basically that give me the optimal
我们是否能够在任何阶段计算出正确的答案
are we going to be able to count the correct answer at any stage don't
correct answer at any stage don't contaminate the other bills and then
污染其他账单，然后反算出什么是
contaminate the other bills and then work backwards figure out what is the
work backwards figure out what is the path that led to God
通往神的道路
我很恶心
work backwards figure out what is the path that led to God
I'm disgusted
所以她非常城市化，他们只是有点老而已
so she was very urbanized they're just old little different
神秘优化感谢与注意
mystical optimizes Thanks versus note
也许这可以使另一个不错的作业好吧，我看到很多漂亮的Chrome
maybe this makes another nice homework by the way ok I see lots of nice chrome
by the way ok I see lots of nice chrome work ok something today
今天工作还可以，所以实际上你知道然后减去
work ok something today ok so actually you know and then minus
ok so actually you know and then minus one and then again city minus one I can
一次，然后再减去一城市，我可以找到最优SAT负2，直到我
one and then again city minus one I can one find the optimal SAT minus 2 until I
one find the optimal SAT minus 2 until I find all the way back to step 1 ok so
找到回到步骤1的所有方法，所以积极地需要做的是
find all the way back to step 1 ok so actively what you need to do is you need
actively what you need to do is you need you know for anybody of like a 50 plus
您知道对于50多岁的人来说，您需要知道什么是最佳选择
you know for anybody of like a 50 plus one you need to know what is the optimal
one you need to know what is the optimal value at the previous step
上一步的价值
各州是因为中国人进行了优化，但最佳状态是整个运行过程中的录像带
one you need to know what is the optimal value at the previous step
the states because the Chinese optimized but the optimal are the tape across run
各州是因为中国人进行了优化，但最佳状态是整个运行过程中的录像带
but the optimal are the tape across run you will be able to go straight to that
您将可以直接进行操作，然后他将继续进行操作，因此
you will be able to go straight to that and then he will continue so the
and then he will continue so the previous step and the previous step on
母老虎的上一步和上一步有一个，然后您就完成了
previous step and the previous step on tigress have one and then you are done
在许多原始元素中，您知道它被用于数百种不同的元素
and in many primitive elements is you know is used in hundreds of different
know is used in hundreds of different applications right you may have heard
您可能听说过的应用程序一词是真实的人，我们告诉
applications right you may have heard the term is a real person that we tell
the term is a real person that we tell the College of Engineering at the UST
你知道的美国科技大学工程学院，所以这是一个真实的人
the College of Engineering at the UST you know so so this is a real person
you know so so this is a real person with a real algorithm it has made lots
凭借真正的算法，它在计算机科学中产生了很大的影响。
with a real algorithm it has made lots of impact in in computer science enjoy
列表中有一个绝对的基本示例，您可能不知道
the list there is an example basic of the absolutely and you may not you know
the absolutely and you may not you know maybe so it will give you another
也许如此，它将给您另一个类似于此的示例让我看看
maybe so it will give you another example similar to this let me see
example similar to this let me see whether it's just a schematic I can
无论是示意图，我都可以指导自己，所以在这里我们有三个
whether it's just a schematic I can guide myself so here we have three
guide myself so here we have three states all right and this is the
陈述所有权利，这是这三个的转移概率
states all right and this is the transition probabilities for the three
transition probabilities for the three states so if you know this state your
陈述，因此，如果您知道该陈述，您的观点即保持此陈述的三分概率
states so if you know this state your point three probability to remain this
point three probability to remain this page 0.7 to go to state two etc etc and
0.7页转到状态二等，这一次的观察概率
page 0.7 to go to state two etc etc and this time the observation probability so
this time the observation probability so if you know state 1 with probability
如果您知道状态1的概率点为5，则可以观察到
if you know state 1 with probability point 5 you can observe see one with
point 5 you can observe see one with probability point two three two and with
概率点二三二和概率2/3等等等，所以你知道
probability point two three two and with probability 2/3 etc etc so you know the
probability 2/3 etc etc so you know the problem is asked you know if you know
问题被问到您是否知道您从状态3开始1对，我们
problem is asked you know if you know that you start in state 3 1 right we
that you start in state 3 1 right we start from there and we have
从那里开始，我们有观察，因为在一切之前
start from there and we have observations because before everything
observations because before everything is a posterior probability so our
是后验概率，因此我们的观察必须回答前提
is a posterior probability so our observations have to answer presupposes
observations have to answer presupposes tricks in first steps
第一步的技巧是保真，所以我们有观察
tricks in first steps it is fidelity so we have observations
it is fidelity so we have observations have G 1 2 3 4 6 6 we know the start
有G 1 2 3 4 6 6我们知道从状态1开始我们知道过渡
have G 1 2 3 4 6 6 we know the start from state 1 we know the transition
from state 1 we know the transition probabilities we know the observation
概率，我们知道观测概率，并告诉您什么时候去
probabilities we know the observation probabilities and tells you when to go
probabilities and tells you when to go out the party let's actually on
在聚会上，让我们实际上是从变量中提取一个谎言，
out the party let's actually on extracting from a variable a lie that
extracting from a variable a lie that you can know everything actually has
您可以知道所有事情实际上都接受过概率论方面的教育
you can know everything actually has education on probabilistic that they are
education on probabilistic that they are very nicely written story recommend but
故事写得很好，值得推荐，但是当你有时间却一无所有时
very nicely written story recommend but when you have time and you have nothing
when you have time and you have nothing else to do
还有其他事情要做
[掌声]
when you have time and you have nothing else to do
[Applause]
这是
this is
对，这样您就可以看到，最终基本上可以在您进行优化时
right so you can see and eventually basically you can optimize when you
basically you can optimize when you reach the entered a website figure out
进入输入的网站，找出这种情况下的最佳产品
reach the entered a website figure out what is the optimal product in this case
what is the optimal product in this case comes to be you know one to two and
变成你知道一二三，我的意思是显然这是一件小事
comes to be you know one to two and three I mean obviously this is a trivial
three I mean obviously this is a trivial problem but you can appreciate trying to
问题，但您可以尝试执行此操作以及更复杂的情况，我们将不胜感激
problem but you can appreciate trying to do this and much more complex scenario
do this and much more complex scenario so there's a very interesting sort of
所以明天会有一个非常有趣的潜水问题
so there's a very interesting sort of diving problem tomorrow
diving problem tomorrow so the main hesitation so I you know any
所以主要的犹豫，所以我通常会在什么时候再次知道任何问题
so the main hesitation so I you know any questions again usually the time to
questions again usually the time to customize
定制大多数情况下接受的可用时间
customize the available most of the days accepting
the available most of the days accepting today ministers from relatives prepare
今天亲戚的传道人今天准备，但是好的，但是明天你可以看到我
today ministers from relatives prepare today but ok but tomorrow you can see me
today but ok but tomorrow you can see me show you how to clear if not it will
告诉您如何清除它是否可以正常工作，所以我会见给您佩斯利
show you how to clear if not it will work right so I'll see you Paisley